[
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8f0",
    "correctAnswer": "Bill Murray",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Jeff Bridges", "John Belushi", "Joe Pesci"],
    "question": "Which actor played the role of Carl Spackler in Caddyshack?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237419dcb85f7ce9e949d78",
    "correctAnswer": "Kathmandu",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Tashkent", "Gaborone", "Gitega"],
    "question": "What is the capital city of Nepal?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950afb",
    "correctAnswer": "B'z",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Buck-Tick", "Southern All Stars", "Babymetal"],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Koshi Inaba'?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f95233a",
    "correctAnswer": "Onion",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Garlic", "Potato", "Tomato"],
    "question": "What Is An Allium Cepa?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950617",
    "correctAnswer": "Zoe Saldana",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Catherine Deneuve", "Audrey Hepburn", "Rachel Weisz"],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Guardians of the Galaxy and Avatar?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504c0",
    "correctAnswer": "prison management and criminal rehabilitation",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "rays, usually ionising radiation",
      "music",
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber"
    ],
    "question": "What is Penology the study of?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fab7",
    "correctAnswer": "Maggie Smith",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dyan Cannon",
      "Penelope Milford",
      "Maureen Stapleton"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 1978 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress for playing the role of Diana Barrie in California Suite?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950036",
    "correctAnswer": "Mark Spitz",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Michael Phelps", "Ian Thorpe", "Matt Biondi"],
    "question": "Who Won 7 gold Medals In Swimming At The 1972 Olympics?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fae5",
    "correctAnswer": "Dustin Hoffman",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Jack Lemmon", "Al Pacino", "Roy Scheider"],
    "question": "Who won the 1979 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Ted Kramer in Kramer vs. Kramer?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95008a",
    "correctAnswer": "Mayfair",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Kensington", "Trafalgar Square", "Old Kent Road"],
    "question": "What Is The Most Valuble Property In A Game Of British Monopoly?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "6384b46f83dddfb71ee5e37d",
    "correctAnswer": "The Hopman Cup",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Indianapolis 500",
      "The Open Championship",
      "The Kentucky Derby"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these is a Tennis competition?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950181",
    "correctAnswer": "James Whistler",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Andy Warhol", "Grant Wood", "Eddie Harold"],
    "question": "Which american artist is known for a portrait of his mother?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f9508b3",
    "correctAnswer": "Oman",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Qatar", "Bahrain", "Iran"],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders United Arab Emirates?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602dda4b176d54800e3caf",
    "correctAnswer": "Indonesia",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Bangladesh", "Thailand", "Mongolia"],
    "question": "Jakarta is a city in which country?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95050e",
    "correctAnswer": "sometimes spelled idealogy, is a system of ideas about politics, human life or culture",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["the characteristics of the skull", "wine", "grasses"],
    "question": "What is Ideology the study of?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62373fafcb85f7ce9e949cb1",
    "correctAnswer": "Bhutan",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Azerbaijan", "Mozambique", "Taiwan"],
    "question": "Thimphu is the capital city of which country?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "623388ca0161109f922aacac",
    "correctAnswer": "The Cantabrian Mountains ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Atlas Mountains",
      "The Alps",
      "The Valencian Mountains"
    ],
    "question": "Which Mountain Range Lies In The North Of Spain?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625fd6a8dc0dd3b72da64d01",
    "correctAnswer": "1981",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1976", "1986", "1991"],
    "question": "In which year was Raiders of the Lost Ark released?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9a1",
    "correctAnswer": "Ulysses",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["My Life As a Man", "On the Road", "Post Office"],
    "question": "Which book contains the character 'Molly Bloom'?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950fbd",
    "correctAnswer": "Elisha Otis",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Marshall Rivet", "Thomas Edison", "Maxwell Hoff"],
    "question": "Who Invented The Elevator?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95069c",
    "correctAnswer": "Jason Bateman",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Javier Bardem", "Colin Firth", "Tim Roth"],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including DodgeBall: A True Underdog Story and Up in the Air?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c41",
    "correctAnswer": "Coldplay",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Level 42", "Deep Purple", "Feeder"],
    "question": "Which British band released the song 'Clocks'?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6237407ecb85f7ce9e949d04",
    "correctAnswer": "Tbilisi",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Beirut", "Bratislava", "Gitega"],
    "question": "What is the capital city of Georgia?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cbf",
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Wings", "Rudimental", "The Alan Parsons Project"],
    "question": "Which English rock band released the album 'The Dark Side of the Moon'?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa17",
    "correctAnswer": "René Magritte",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["‎Salvador Dalí", "Sandro Botticelli", "Raphael"],
    "question": "Which artist painted \"The Son of Man\"",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c60bc50d1a5e051325a70",
    "correctAnswer": "Japan",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Turkey", "Spain", "Estonia"],
    "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Sushi?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951888",
    "correctAnswer": "1973",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1930", "1891", "1990"],
    "question": "In What year did British Honduras become Belize?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503b9",
    "correctAnswer": "New Mexico",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Nagasaki", "Hiroshima", "Bikini Atoll"],
    "question": "Where did the first atomic bomb explode?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff5d",
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Dylan",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Neil Young", "Eric Clapton", "Alanis Morissette"],
    "question": "Which American musician released the album 'Highway 61 Revisited'?",
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": []
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c64",
    "correctAnswer": "Perestroika",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Apparatchik", "Uskoreniye", "Khozraschyot"],
    "question": "After the fall of the iron curtain, Russian leader Mikhail Gorbachev introduced a period of restructuring known as what?"
  }
]
